const questions=[
    {
        question:"Javascript is an _______ language?",
        answers:["Object-Oriented","Object-Based","Procedural","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        answers:["var","let","Both A and B ","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:2
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        answers:["getElementById()","getElementByClassName()","Both A and B ","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:2
    },
    {
        question:"Upcoming encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
        answers:["Throws an error","Ignores the statements","Giving a warning,,"None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:1
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
        answers:["document.write()","console.log()","window.alert()","All of the above"],
        correctAnswer:3
    },
    {
        question:"How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        answers:["const","var","let","constant"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
        answers:["in","is in","exits","lies"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
        answers:["The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers.","Clears all the cookies and cache.","Both A and B","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
        answers:["Boolean","Undefined","Object","Integer"],
        correctAnswer:2
    },
    {
        question:"What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
        answers:["It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime.","It acts as a breakpoint in a program.","It will debug error in the current statement if any.","All of the above"],
        correctAnswer:1
    },
    {
        question:"What does the ‘toLocateString()’ method do in JS?",
        answers:["Returns a localised object representation.","Returns a parses string.","Returns a localized string representation of an object.","None of the above."],
        correctAnswer:2
    },
    {
        question:"The process in which an object or data structure is translated into a format suitable for transferral over a network, or storage is called?",
        answers:["Object Serialization","Object Encapsulation","Object Inheritance","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        answers:["stringify()","parse()","convert()","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"The 3 basic object attributes in Javascript are:",
        answers:["Class,prototype,object's paramenters.","Class, prototype, object's extensible flag","Class,parameters, object's extensible flag","Classes, Native object, and Interfaces"],
        correctAnswer:1
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
        answers:["Variables","Functions","Objects","All of the above"],
        correctAnswer:3
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
        answers:["Node","Vue","React","Cassandra"],
        correctAnswer:3
    },
    {
        question:"What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
        answers:["async","await","setTimeout","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
        answers:["clearInterval","clearTimer","intervalOver","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"How are objects compared when they are checked with the strict equality operator?",
        answers:["The contents of the objects are compared","Their references are compared","Both A and B","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:1
    },
    {
        question:"What does … operator do in JS?",
        answers:["It is used to spread iterables to individual elements","It is used to describe a datatype of undefined size","No such operator exists","None of the above"],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"How do we write a comment in javascript?",
        answers:["/* */","//","#","$ $"],
        correctAnswer:1
    },
    {
        question:"Which object in Javascript doesn’t have a prototype?",
        answers:["Base Object","All objects have a prototype","None of the objects have a prototype",""],
        correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
        question:"Which of  the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
        answers:["Date","FileUpload","Function","All of the above"],
        correctAnswer:3
    }

    
]